you know, Shirley Raines is the best of us because she's somebody who genuinely was like,
I am having a terrible time in the world and it's not going to stop me from being my best
in the world. And that's what I mean by alchemizing, right? Like that's what I mean by
taking your fear and alchemizing it into something valuable. And, you know, that's not always going
to be possible, but I think the effort is something worth denoting. And, you know, Shirley Raines
is a great example of that, of somebody who said, you know, I, she sat on my couch,
she sat on my couch and she said, you know, I just, I really have a tough time. And I feel very
fortunate to have gotten to spend time with somebody who was doing that work because I feel
like that's the type of stuff that you can't just make up. You need to see it modeled. And I was very
fortunate to get to experience that in real time with her. I was, I was able to see it modeled in
real time. And, um, you know, so we, we will continue to lift her up and lift those up who
are living and modeling in real time, what that is. I want y'all to know, like what we may be losing
as folks who are still here on earth, that person may be gaining in relief. And I don't know if Ms.
Shirley, I don't know the, I don't know the, um, circumstances of her passing, but I do know
that she was a soul that was very, very in pain. And the first thing that came to me when I saw this
was she gets to see her son. Those souls will get to connect again. So when I say rest in peace
to Ms. Shirley, I mean that literally.